

JORDI HAFIDZ AZIS

Bekasi, Jawa Barat, 17155 | 0851 5755 2314 | jordihafidz2908@gmail.com

About Me

I am Jordi Hafidz Azis, an individual who is full of interest and enthusiasm for coffee. Besides, I have a desire to learn about different coffee drinks and how to serve them well. I want to be a barista who is friendly, communicative, and ready to provide a satisfying coffee experience for every customer. I have high dedication at work, honest, responsive, have good communication skills, adaptable, like to learn new things. As well as having high motivation to always learn in order to develop my potential

Education

Universitas Darma Persada (2020 - Now)

S1 Information Technology

• Mastering programming knowledge such as Front-end and Back-end in developing websites.

Work Experience

DelapanDua Kopi (Juli 2021 – November 2021) Tandaso Café and Resto (Februari 2023 – Juli 2023)

Skill

- greetings to customers
- able to operate a coffee machine
- can make latte art
- can make manual brew